Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Joseph O'Donnell Papers, 1947-1987 and undated, bulk 1986
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches, 1983-1986 and undated, (4 boxes)
  - Operation Managers Group presentation slides, 1986 Aug. 14 (Box 16)
  - Responsibility of Annual Manager, circa 1984 (Box 17)
  - Roots of Communication, 1985 Mar. (Box 17)
  - Senior Vice Presidents, 1983 (Box 17)
  - State of the Agency, 1983 Aug. 3 (Box 17)
  - Unidentified speech, undated (Box 17)
  - Vancouver talk, 1986 Oct. 14-16 (Box 17)
  - Vice Presidents, undated (Box 17)
  - What Chicago Did to Advertising, undated (Box 17)
  - What We Have Learned, 1984 May (Box 17)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1985-1986 [RESTRICTED], (1 box)
  Series includes film compilations of advertising spots of JWT clients, as well as clients of competitive companies. Arranged alphabetically by title.
  [Restrictions on access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be made]
  - Board of Directors Reel. Format: Umatic. 1986 Sept. 11, (2 copies) (Box 18)
    [Includes spots for Kodak, Union Carbide, Warner-Lambert, Diet-Pepsi, Teledyne Shower Massage, Bacardi, Winston, British Telecom, Burger King, Goodyear, R.T. French, Miller and Ford. Offices represented include Asia/Pacific, Canada, Latin America, Europe and U.S.A.
  - J. Walter Does That, Canadian version. Format: Betamax. Undated. (Box 18)
  - Trends in U.S. Advertising. Format: Betamax. 1986 Oct. (Box 18)
    [Includes spots for Health & Tennis, Pepsi Slice, Kraft Singles, Kellogg All Bran, Reynold's Wrap, and Ford Mustang. Also includes music video for Peter Gabriel's song Sledgehammer].
  - What Chicago Did to Advertising
    - Burt Manning version. Format: Betamax. 1985 Oct. 24 (Box 18)
    - Joe O'Donnell version. Format: Betamax. 1985 Oct. 24, (2 copies) (Box 18)
      [Includes spots for Kraft TV Theater and Cheez Whiz, Marlboro, Keebler, Alka Seltzer, Mr. Clean, Coast, Hallmark, Raid, Coors, McDonald's, Wheaties, Seven-Up, Sears, Oscar Mayer and Quaker.]